{
    "subject": "resource/William_F._Allen_(Delaware)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Bridgeville,_Delaware",
    "human_readable": "William F. Allen (Delaware) was born in Bridgeville, Delaware.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9492152333259583,
            "question": "Is William F. Allen from Bridgeville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9206879734992981,
            "question": "Where was William F. Allen born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8795148730278015,
            "question": "Is Bridgeville a city in Delaware?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8785914182662964,
            "question": "Where was William F. Allen from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8668777942657471,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where William F. Allen was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7709224820137024,
            "question": "In which state did William F. Allen reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7352334856987,
            "question": "What state is associated with William F. Allen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7316122055053711,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about William F. Allen's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.674919605255127,
            "question": "What is the name of the state associated with William F. Allen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.67491614818573,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Delaware and William F. Allen?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=William F. Allen (Delaware) was born in Bridgeville, Delaware.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3221_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the state associated with William F. Allen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3221_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about William F. Allen's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3221_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is associated with William F. Allen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3221_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3221_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3221_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3221_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3221_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3221_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3221_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3221_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3221_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3221_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3221_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about William Franklin Allen\u2019s birthplace as Bridgeville, Delaware, which supports the statement that William F. Allen (Delaware) was born in Bridgeville, Delaware."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}